# Anders G. Nordby



## KEY COMPETENCIES

(+47) 932 20 333

anders@delichon.no

Processes

C

 $\leq$ 

Systems Architecture, Scrum, Kanban, Project Management.

https://www.linkedin.com/in/agnordby/

Updated version of this dokument:

https://github.com/agnordby/cv Barcelona (One week pr month in Oslo)

Development

C#, Akka.Net, GraphQL, NHibernate, Blazor, Gherkin, Specflow, Cypress, NUnit, Moq, Kiuwan, PowerBI, log4net, Episerver, ASP.Net, SQL, Javascript, NServiceBus, REST, Powershell, LATEX.

Tools

Jira, Confluence, TeamCity, Octopus Deploy, Git, TFS, SubVersion, NewRelic, jMeter, BlazeMeter, NuGet, Kiuwan.

#### CERTIFICATIONS

**Certified Optimizely Developer** 2.02.0

Microsoft AZ900 Azure Fundamentals

**PRINCE2 Practitioner** 2019 **Certified Scrum Master** 2019

**PRINCE2 Foundation** 2.018

#### COURSES

Building an AppSec Scanning Programme 2024

Tom Gilb: Architecture Workshop 2019

Sopra Steria: Arkitekturskolen 2018

Microsoft: Lead Enterprise Architect Programme 2015

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Oslo, Teacher Training 2003 - 2004 Oslo Business Academy, IT Candidate 1999 – 2000 University of Oslo, Cand.Mag. 1987 – 1996 Eikeli High School, Natural Sciences 1984 - 1987

### **AWARDS**

**Episerver Most Valued Professional** 2013-2017

#### **LANGUAGES**

Norwegian (native), English EXCELLENT INTERMEDIATE Bulgarian, German Spanish, Japanese BEGINNER

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Systems Architect and Senior Developer with 20+ years of experience designing scalable software solutions across industries. Specialized in application security, distributed systems, and modern architecture. Proven leader in team coordination, agile practices, and security governance.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2019 - PRESENT

Delichon AS

Systems Architect & Senior Developer

Customer: Element Logic **Duration:** 5 years

Roles: Senior Systems Developer, Security Champion

Technologies: C#, Akka.NET, Blazor, REST, GraphQL, NHibernate, SQL, NUnit, Moq, Microsoft .NET Standard, ASP.NET, TeamCity,

Octopus Deploy, Git, Powershell, Kiuwan.

Responsibility: Senior developer on Element Logic's main product, eManager. Additionally, focuses on application security, and is the initiator and leader for Element Logic's Security Chapions Guild.

**Customer:** ABB

Role: Senior Systems Developer

**Duration:** 6 months

**Technologies:** Azure DevOps, Azure DB, Azure WebServices, Akka.NET, TypeScript, React JS, C#, Microsoft .NET Core, TFS, Git, Powershell.

01/2018 - 04/2019

Sopra Steria

## Lead Software Engineer

Roles: In-house architect responsible for planning and QA of offers to customers. Senior developer for some customers.

Customers: Skatteetaten, Helsedirektoratet.

Technologies: C#, .Net, Episerver CMS, ASP.NET MVC, Microsoft SQL Server, JavaScript, Jira, Confluence, TFS, Git.

03/2014 - 08/2017

**CGI** 

## Senior Web Developer

Roles: Team Leader, Scrum Master, Hands-on Architect. Customers: ASKO, Fellesforbundet, Tekna, PIA, Miljødirektoratet. Technologies: C#, inRiver PIM, Apptus eSales, Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, IdentityServer, T-SQL, NServiceBus, Jira, Confluence, jMeter, BlazeMeter, Angular.js, Knockout.js.

03/2010 - 01/2014 08/2008 - 12/2009 02/2006 - 07/2008 10/2004 - 02/2008 05/1995 - 06/2002

Making Waves, Senior Systems Consultant Creuna, Consultant / Systems Developer Ocelluz, Systems Developer & Project Manager Anders Nordby Konsulenttjenester Ajilon, Consultant